desktimeapp.com 2017-06-17

# Privacy Policy – Desktime

Effective Date: July 6, 2015

This privacy policy (hereafter “Privacy Policy”) applies to the Website(s) and the Services (as such terms are defined in the Company’s Terms of Service). The Terms of Service can be found at the following link: https://www.desktimeapp.com/privacy. All capitalized terms in this Privacy Policy will have the meanings assigned to them in the Terms of Service; and the Company is also referred to in this Privacy Policy as “We”, “Us”, “Our” and similar capitalized terms.

### 1\. General

We respect Your privacy and We are committed to protecting personally identifiable information that may be accessed or submitted through the Website(s). We have adopted this Privacy Policy to explain what information may be collected on our Website(s), how We may use this information, and under what circumstances We may disclose the information to third parties.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information We collect through the Website(s), and does not apply to our collection of information from any other sources. We keep this Privacy Policy posted on the Website(s) and you should review it frequently, as it may change from time to time without notice. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy.

WHEN YOU ACCESS OUR WEBSITE(S) AND/OR USE THE SERVICES YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AS PART OF THE AGREEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, OR TO ANY CHANGES WE MAY SUBSEQUENTLY MAKE, IMMEDIATELY STOP ACCESSING OUR WEBSITE(S).

### 2\. Information We May Collect

Our Website(s) typically collect two kinds of information about You: (a) information that You voluntarily provide which may personally identify You; and (b) general information relating to your use of the Website(s) that does not personally identify You and that We automatically collect when You visit our Website(s).

  1. Personally Identifiable Information: For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, Our definition of personally identifiable information includes any information that may be used to specifically identify or contact you, such as your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, etc. (“PII”). As a general policy, We do not require users to provide Us with any PII in order to use certain portions of the Website(s); However, certain information may required of you if you wish to register to use the Services, and portions of that information may be PII.
  2. Non-Personal Information: Our definition of non-personal information includes any information that does not personally identify You (“Non-PII”). Non-personal information can include certain personally identifiable information that has been de-identified; that is, information that has been rendered anonymous. We may obtain non-personal information about you from information that you may provide to us (e.g. by submitting a contact request, etc.), either separately or together with your PII. We also automatically collect certain Non-PII from you when you access our Websites. This information can include, among other things, IP addresses, the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, etc.), the third party website from which your visit originated, the operating system you are using (e.g., Vista, Windows XP, Macintosh OS, etc.), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, NetZero, etc.), the specific areas of the Website that you visit, the duration of your visit, and other general information.

### 3\. How We Use and Share Information

  1. Personally Identifiable Information: As noted above, We do not require any PII to access or use certain areas on the Website(s). If You do provide Us with PII (E.g. by submitting a contact request, or registering on the Website(s)) You agree that We may also use this information to later contact you for a variety of reasons, such as customer service, providing you promotional information about our products and services or those of our other affiliated companies or to communicate with you about the Services. Information that You voluntarily post in any comment or feedback feature maintained on the Website(s) is not PII and is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

In certain instances We may share your PII with third party service partners which are under contract with Us and which perform Website-related functions on our behalf, e.g., vendors that provide Us with credit card processing services, assist us with customer service, etc.

Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, your personally identifiable information will not be shared or sold to any third parties without your prior approval.

  2. Non-Personal Information: We use Non-PII in a variety of ways, including to help analyze site traffic, understand customer needs and trends, carry out targeted promotional activities, and to improve our services. We may use your Non-PII by itself or aggregate it with information We have obtained from others. We may share your non-personal information with our affiliated companies and third parties to achieve these objectives and others, but remember that aggregate information is anonymous information that does not personally identify You. 
  3. IP Addresses: We may collect IP addresses for purposes of system administration, to report non-personal aggregate information to others, and to track the use of our Website(s). IP addresses are considered non-personal information and may also be shared as provided above. We reserve the right to use IP addresses and any personally identifiable information to identify a visitor when We feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Service or to: (a) fulfill a government request; (b) conform with the requirements of the law or legal process; (c) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our Website(s), or other users; or (d) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of our Website(s)’ users or the general public.
  4. Cookies: We may, from time to time, use cookies (small text files that do not contain PII) in connection with our Website(s); and We may analyze the information derived from these cookies for the same purposes as set forth in Section 2.C of this Privacy Policy. You may be able to limit the use of cookies on your computer or mobile device in general by modifying the settings of your web browser (e.g. Internet Explorer, Chrome, etc.). Please note, however, that some parts of our Website(s) may not function properly or be available to you if you refuse to accept a cookie or choose to disable the acceptance of cookies.
  5. Flash Cookies: From time to time We may use Flash cookies to store Your preferences (e.g. volume control) or to display content based upon what You view on our site to personalize Your visit. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the type and manner in which data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, go to: 

<http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

  6. Email Communications: If You send Us an email with questions or comments, We may use Your PII to respond to Your questions or comments, and We may save your questions or comments for future reference. For security reasons, We do not recommend that You send non-public personal information, such as passwords, social security numbers, or bank account information, to us by email. However, aside from Our reply to such an email, we will not send You email unless: (1) you request a particular service or sign up for a feature that involves email communications, (2) We are sending you information about our Services, and/or (3) You consented to being contacted by email for a particular purpose.
  7. Transfer of Assets: As We continue to develop our business, We may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or all (or substantially all) of our assets, the PII and Non-PII We have about You will be transferred to and used by this acquiring entity. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, all such information may be considered an asset of Ours and as such may be sold or transferred to third parties.
  8. Children, Parental Consent, and Privacy: The Website(s) are not directed toward children under age 13. We do not knowingly collect information from anyone under age 13. If We find out that We have collected information from a child under age 13, We will delete that information immediately. 
  9. Social Media Links: The Website(s) may integrate with social media services (e.g. Facebook) using features or tools which let you voluntarily share Your activities or opinions related to the Services on such social media services. These features and/or tools may enable the sharing of information with the public, depending on the settings you establish with the social media service provider. These features/tools may collect your IP address and a record of the page(s) You visit, and may also attempt to install a cookie (see 3.D, above) or similar file. Your use of these features/tools is governed by the terms of Section 5 of this Privacy Policy. 
  10. Advertising: We may use or allow third-party companies to generate advertisements on the Website(s). Such companies may use cookies (see section 3.D) or similar technologies to tailor the advertisements you see on the Website(s) and to track your response (if any) to their advertisement. The cookies do not contain or generate any PII.
  11. Other: Notwithstanding anything herein to the contrary, We reserve the right to disclose any PII or Non-PII about You if We are required to do so by law, with respect to copyright or other intellectual property infringement claims, or if We believe that such action is necessary to: (1) fulfill a government request; (2) conform with the requirements of the law or legal process; (3) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our Website(s), or other users; or (4) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of our Website's users or the general public. 

### 4\. Information Security

We have implemented security measures We consider reasonable and appropriate to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under Our control. Please be advised, however, We cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your PII. 

### 5\. Third Party Sites

We are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or security practices employed by any third party website or service, including but not limited to any such sites or services that may be linked to or referred to in any way on the Website(s).

### 6\. Contact Information

You may contact Us as provided below if: (a) you have questions or comments about our Privacy Policy; (b) wish to make corrections to any PII you have provided; or (c) if you have voluntarily submitted your contact information to Us, and you want to opt-out from receiving future promotional correspondence, including emails, from us or our affiliated companies; [](mailto:info@desktimeapp.com)

We will respond to Your request and, if applicable and appropriate, make the requested changes as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that We may not be able to fulfill certain requests while allowing you access to certain benefits, features and services offered on or through our Website(s).
